A Guide to the Papers of Dr. Edward Watson Hook, Jr., 1947-1998
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- SERIES 4: Office Files, alphabetically arranged
  - Students February 1980-December 1982, 4 TL, 13 TLS, 1 TMemo, 10 TD, 1 TN, 1 TMs (Box-folder 040-004)
    Re: Student clerckships, evaluations, grading system, and a student study, "Assessing Rapport in the Tertiary Care Setting."
  - University President's Office, Correspondence October 1974-April 1988, 1 TMemo, 4 TL, 16 TLS (Box-folder 040-005)
    Re: Hook's correspondence with UVa's president's office - name suggestions for committees and UVa President.
- SERIES 5: Photgraphs & Artifacts
  - [Medical School Class of 1873, in front of Anatomical Hall] [1873], 1 photo (Box-folder 041-001)
  - [Dr. Steven A. Newman], [Dr. Edward W. Hook], & two unidentified people [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 041-002)
  - Congressman [Paul Rogers], [Dr. Robert M. Carey], [s.n.], [Dr. Edward W. Hook], & [Admiral & Mrs. Freeman Carey] [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 041-003)
  - 4 unidentified people & [Mary Wagner? 3rd from r.] [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 041-004)
  - [Dr. Edward W. Hook] and Congressman [Paul Rogers] [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 041-005)
  - 3 unidentifed men with [Dr. Edward W. Hook] [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 041-006)
  - Congressman [Paul Rogers] [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 041-007)
  - 2 unidentified people with Congressman [Paul Rogers] [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 041-008)
  - Unidentified woman with Congressman [Paul Rogers] [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 041-009)
  - [Dr. Robert M. Carey], unidentified woman, Congressman [Paul Rogers] [n.d.] (Box-folder 041-010)
  - [Jesse Hook], unidentified man & woman [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 041-011)
  - Photograph of a sheet of negatives of the 1978 Staige Blackford Lecture 1978, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-012)
  - 1978 Staige Blackford Lecture - 2 unidentified men 1978, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-013)
  - 1978 Staige Blackford Lecture, 5 unidentified men [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 041-014)
  - 1978 Staige Blackford Lecture, 7 unidentified people 1978, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-015)
  - 1978 Staige Blackford Lecture, Rotunda in evening 1978, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-016)
  - 1978 Staige Blackford Lecture, 3 unidentified individuals 1978, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-017)
  - 1978 Staige Blackford Lecture, [Dr. Edward W. Hook] & 2 unidentified men 1978, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-018)
  - 1978 Staige Blackford Lecture, [Dr. Edward W. & Jesse Hook] with 4 unidentified individuals 1978, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-019)
  - 1978 Staige Blackford Lecture, [Dr. Edward W. Hook] with 2 unidentified men 1978, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-020)
  - 1978 Staige Blackford Lecture, 4 individuals by Jefferson statue in Rotunda 1978, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-021)
  - 1978 Staige Blackford Lecture, 3 unidentified people 1978, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-022)
  - RAC 1977 Notebook, 6 unidentifed men 1977, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-023)
  - RAC 1977 Notebook, [Dr. Edward W. Hook] & 5 unidentified men 1977, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-024)
  - RAC 1977 Notebook, 7 unidentified men 1977, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-025)
  - RAC 1977 Notebook, negatives of photos 1977, 1 nagative strip (Box-folder 041-026)
  - RAC 1977 Notebook, negatives of photos 1977, 1 negative strip (Box-folder 041-027)
  - Andrew De Jarnette Hart Conference Room [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 041-028)
  - [Andrew De Jarnette Hart] with [unknown] by door of Andrew De Jarnette Hart Conference Room [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 041-029)
  - [Andrew De Jarnette Hart] with [unknown] in Andrew De Jarnette Hart Conference Room [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 041-030)
  - 4 individuals viewing chest X-rays in the Andrew De Jarnette Conference Room [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 041-031)
  - Photo of all negatives of Andrew De Jarnette Conference Room [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 041-032)
  - 3 negatives of Andrew De Jarnette Conference Room [n.d.], 1 negative strip (Box-folder 041-033)
  - 4 negatives of Andrew De Jarnette Conference Room [n.d.], 1 negative strip (Box-folder 041-034)
  - 4 negatives of Andrew De Jarnette Conference Room [n.d.], 1 negative strip (Box-folder 041-035)
  - Picture of House Staff & Department of Internal Medicine, 1948 May 21, 1948, 3 negatives, 1 envelope (Box-folder 041-036)
  - 1958-59? Department of Medicine Faculty & Housestaff [1958-59?], 2 photos (Box-folder 041-037)
  - 1960-61 Department of Medicine Faculty & Housestaff 1960-1961, 3 photos (Box-folder 041-038)
  - 1965-66? Department of Medicine Faculty & Housestaff [1965-66?], 1 photo (Box-folder 041-039)
  - 1966-67 Department of Medicine Faculty and Housestaff 1966-67, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-040)
  - 1966-67 Department of Medicine Faculty & Staff 1966-67, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-041)
  - 1967-68 Deparment of Medicine Faculty & Housestaff 1967-68, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-042)
  - 1967-68 Department of Medicine 1967-68, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-043)
  - 3 unidentified men 1967-68, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-044)
  - 3 unidentified men 1967-68, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-045)
  - 3 unidentified men 1967-68, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-046)
  - 1968-69 Deparment of Medicine Faculty & Housestaff 1968-69, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-047)
  - 1971-72 Department of Medicine Faculty & Housestaff 1971-72, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-048)
  - 1972-73 Department of Medicine Faculty & Housestaff 1972-73, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-049)
  - 1 photo (Box-folder 041-0)
  - 1972-73 Department of Medicine Faculty & Housestaff 1972-73, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-050)
  - 1973-74 Department of Medicine Faculty & Housestaff 1973-74, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-051)
  - 1973-74 Department of Medicine Faculty & Housestaff 1973-74, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-052)
  - 1975-76 Department of Medicine Faculty & Housestaff 1975-76, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-053)
  - [unknown], [Dr. Edward W. Hook], R.L. Thompson 1975-76, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-054)
  - 1975 Department of Medicine Faculty & Housestaff 1975, 1 TD, 1 neg., 1 photo (Box-folder 041-055)
  - 1975 Department of Medicine Faculty & Housestaff 1975, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-056)
  - [George Craddock], [Edward W. Hook], [Dwight Wooster] 1975, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-057)
  - Dr. Edward W. Hook & [Dr. Julian Beckwith] 1976-77, 2 photos (Box-folder 041-058)
  - Edward W. Hook shaking the hand of [Dr. Julian Beckwith] 1976-77, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-059)
  - [Dr. John Zirkle], [Dr. Edward W. Hook], [Dr. Richard Keeling] 1976-77, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-060)
  - [Dr. John Zirkle], [Dr. Edward W. Hook], [Dr. Richard Keeling] 1976-77, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-061)
  - House Staff-Teaching Staff, V.A. Hospital Medical Service, Salem, Va 1976-77 1976-77, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-062)
  - 1978-79 Department of Medicine, University of Virginia Medical School 1978, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-063)
  - Dr. Robert Gibson, Dr. Merle Sande, & Dr. Oksana Korzenowski 1978, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-064)
  - Dr. J.T. Bowers, Dr. Edward W. Hook, and Dr. W.J. Oblinger [1978], 1 photo (Box-folder 041-065)
  - Dr. S.C. Foote & Dr. Edward W. Hook 1977-78, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-066)
  - 1977-78 Department of Medicine Faculty and Housestaff 1977=78, 2 photos, 2 TD (Box-folder 041-067)
  - 1979-1980 Department of Medicine Group Picture 1979-80, 2 photo, 1 TD (Box-folder 041-068)
  - 1980-81 Department of Medicine Group Photograph 1981, 2 negatives, 1 TD, 2 photos (Box-folder 041-069)
  - Printed images of 3 negatives of 1980-81 Department of Medicine Group Photos 1981, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-070)
  - 1980-81 Chief Residents, Richard Gualtieri, Gary C. Murray, & Edward W. Hook May 1981, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-071)
  - Printed images of 3 negatives of 1980-81 Chief Residents with Edward W. Hook [May 1981], 1 photo, 1 negatives (Box-folder 041-072)
  - 1981-82 Department of Medicine Group Photograph [May] 1982, 3 photo, 1 TD (Box-folder 041-073)
  - Chief Residents 1981-82, [Carl D. Malchoff], [Edward W. Hook], [Robert E. Boyd] 1981-1982, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-074)
  - Chief Residents 1981-82, Carl D. Malchoff, Robert E. Boyd, & Edward W. Hook 1981-1982, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-075)
  - 1982-1983 Department of Medicine Group Photo May 1983, 2 photo, 1 TD, 1 negative (Box-folder 041-076)
  - [Edward W. Hook], [Michael Collins], and [Michael Williams] May 1983, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-077)
  - [Edward W. Hook], [John B.] Schorling, [Donald R.] Lilly, [Munsey S. Wheby] 1983-1984, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-078)
  - Edward W. Hook, Donald R. Lilly, John B. Schorling, & Munsey S. Wheby 1983-1984, 2 photo (Box-folder 041-079)
  - 1983-84 Department of Medicine 1983-1984, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-080)
  - 1983-84 Department of Medicine Photograph May 1984, 4 photo, 1 AD, 1 TD (Box-folder 041-081)
  - 1985 Departmental group picture 1985, 3 photo, 1 TD (Box-folder 041-082)
  - 3 negatives of 1985 Departmental Group Photos 1985, 1 negative strip (Box-folder 041-083)
  - 1986 Department of Medicine Group Photo [May 12], 1986, 2 photo, 1 TD (Box-folder 041-084)
  - 4 negatives of individuals & small group photos of 1986 1986, 1 negative strip (Box-folder 041-085)
  - 4 negatives of 1986 Department of Medicine Group Photo 1986, 1 negative strip (Box-folder 041-086)
  - 1987 Department of Medicine 1987, 2 photo, 1 TD (Box-folder 041-087)
  - 1988-89 Department of Medicine Faculty & Housestaff 1988-1989, 2 photo, 1 AN (Box-folder 041-088)
  - [Dr. Edward W. Hook], [Dr. R. Smith], [Dr. B. Robinson], & [Dr. Munsey S. Wheby] 1988-1989, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-089)
  - [Dr. Munsey S. Wheby], [Dr. Auredeo], [Dr. Benitez], unknown man, [Dr. R. Smith], [Dr. Edward W. Hook] [1988 or 1989] ], 2 photo (Box-folder 041-090)
  - Dr. Munsey S. Wheby, Dr. Walter Smalley, Dr. Nicholas [Demaria?], Dr. Edward W. Hook 1988-1989, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-091)
  - Dr. Munsey S. Wheby, Dr. Walter Smalley, Dr. Edward W. Hook, & Dr. Nicholas [Demaria?] 1988-1989, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-092)
  - Dr. Munsey S. Wheby, Dr. Kevin High, Dr. Coleen McNamara, Dr. Edward W. Hook 1988-1989, 2 photo (Box-folder 041-093)
  - Dr. Munsey S. Wheby, Dr. Kevin High, Dr. Coleen McNamara, Dr. Edward W. Hook 1988-1989, 2 photo (Box-folder 041-094)
  - 1988-89 Department of Medicine Faculty & Housestaff 1988-1989, 2 photo (Box-folder 041-095)
  - 1989 Department of Medicine 1989, 1 photo (Box-folder 041-096)
  - 5 negatives of 1988-89 Department of Medicine photographs 1988-1989, 1 negative strip (Box-folder 041-097)
  - [Mrs. Freeman Carey], [Admiral Freeman Carey], [Jesse Hook], & [Dr. Edward W. Hook] [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 041-098)
  - Edward W. Hook, Jr., M.D. [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-001)
  - Edward W. Hook, Jr., M.D. [n.d.], 1 negative (Box-folder 042-002)
  - Pink Ladies Canteen with Mrs. Townsend, Mrs. Hayes, [Elizabeth Gamble] Mulholland 1951, 1 photo (Box-folder 042-003)
  - Edward W. Hook, Jr. M.D. [n.d.], 1 negative (Box-folder 042-004)
  - Meeting of Research & Engineering Advisory Panel on Biological & Chemical Defense at Naval Biological Laboratory October, 1960, 1 photo (Box-folder 042-005)
  - 1978 ACP Regional Meeting 1978, 1 photo, 1 AN (Box-folder 042-006)
  - 1978 ACP Regional Meeting 1978, 1 photo (Box-folder 042-007)
  - 1978 ACP Regional Meeting 1978, 1 photo (Box-folder 042-008)
  - 1978 ACP Regional Meeting 1978, 1 photo (Box-folder 042-009)
  - Edward W. Hook as President, Infectious Disease Society of America 1975-1976, 1 photo (Box-folder 042-010)
  - Edward W. Hook as President, Infectious Disease Society of America 1975-1976, 1 photo (Box-folder 042-011)
  - Edward W. Hook as President, Infectious Disease Society of America 1975-1976, 1 photo (Box-folder 042-012)
  - Edward W. Hook as President, Infectious Disease Society of America 1975-1976, 1 photo (Box-folder 042-013)
  - Edward W. Hook as President-elect, Infectious Disease Society of America 1974-1975, 1 photo, 1 newspaper clipping (Box-folder 042-014)
  - Edward W. Hook as President-elect, Infectious Disease Society of America, 1 photo (Box-folder 042-015)
  - Rotunda, University of Virginia [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-016)
  - unidentified man [1977], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-017)
  - 2 unidentified men [1977], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-018)
  - Physicians & Staff of the Medical School [1977], 2 photo (Box-folder 042-019)
  - [Charles L.] Crockett [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-020)
  - [Charles L.] Crockett & 5 other doctors February 1966, 1 photo (Box-folder 042-021)
  - 1976 Rheumatology Division 1976, 1 photo (Box-folder 042-022)
  - Rheumotology Division 1977, 1 photo (Box-folder 042-023)
  - Division of Endocrinology & Metabolism July 1978, 1 photo, 1 AN (Box-folder 042-024)
  - Unidentified doctors & nurses gathered around a patient March 27, 1959, 1 photo (Box-folder 042-025)
  - [Dr. Bram Rose], [Oscar] Swineford [Jr.], [John L.] Guerrant Spring 1962, 2 photo (Box-folder 042-026)
  - 14 unidentified men gathered around a table [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-027)
  - [Dr. Oscar Swineford, Jr.] with 3 unidentified men [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-028)
  - [Oscar Swineford, Jr.] with 13 unidentified men, 2 photo (Box-folder 042-029)
  - Dr. [Oscar Swineford, Jr.] Spring 1962, 2 photo (Box-folder 042-030)
  - [Dr. Oscar Swineford, Jr.] [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-031)
  - Dr. [Oscar] Swineford, Jr. [1967?], 3 photo, 1 AN (Box-folder 042-032)
  - Former Allergy Fellows April 1966, 1 photo (Box-folder 042-033)
  - 3 unidentified men with [Dr. Oscar Swineford, Jr.] at Allergy Conference April 28, 1967, 1 photo, 1 AN (Box-folder 042-034)
  - 18 unidentified men toasting [Dr. Oscar Swineford, Jr.] [April 28, 1967], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-035)
  - [Dr. Oscar Swineford, Jr.] [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-036)
  - 19 individuals at Allergy Conference [April 28, 1967], 1 photo, 3 AN (Box-folder 042-037)
  - [Dr. Thomas H.] Hunter's porch September 14, 1997, 2 photo (Box-folder 042-038)
  - A very ill [Dr. Thomas H. Hunter] September 14, 1997, 2 photo (Box-folder 042-039)
  - [Dr. Thomas H. Hunter] being interviewed September 14, 1997, 2 photo (Box-folder 042-040)
  - Drawing of Thomas H. Hunter resting 1993, 1 photo, 1 negative (Box-folder 042-041)
  - Launcelot Fleming [n.d.], 1 photo, 1 negative (Box-folder 042-042)
  - Thomas H. & Anne F. Hunter coming out of the Brighton May 1946, 1 photo, 1 negative (Box-folder 042-043)
  - Thomas H. Hunter & family; wife - Anne, children - Charles, Betty, Bill, Tom Scott, & Peter Summer 1955, 1 photo, 1 negative, 1 AN (Box-folder 042-044)
  - Thomas H. Hunter with Ted Phelps on Tideway [n.d.], 1 photo, 1 negative (Box-folder 042-045)
  - [Dr. Thomas H. Hunter] [n.d.], 1 photo, 1 negative (Box-folder 042-046)
  - Argyra White Hunter with Thomas H. Hunter 1915, 2 photo, 1 negative (Box-folder 042-047)
  - Thomas H. Hunter in a wagon, Madison Park, Chicago 1915, 2 photo, 1 negative (Box-folder 042-048)
  - Thomas H. Hunter on a tricycle at Christmas time [December] 1916, 2 photo, 1 negative (Box-folder 042-049)
  - Thomas H. Hunter with grandparents Llewelyn Kidder Hunter & Jessie Lorine? Hunter Summer 1916, 1 neg, 2 photo (Box-folder 042-050)
  - Thomas H. Hunter & Llewelyn Kidder Hunter in potato patch, Baron Lake, MI 1917 or 1918, 2 photo, 1 neg (Box-folder 042-051)
  - Thomas H. Hunter in a cart pulled by a horse [n.d.], 1 neg, 2 photo (Box-folder 042-052)
  - Belmont Hill School in about 1924 or 1925 1924 or 1925, 1 photo, 1 neg (Box-folder 042-053)
  - Thomas H. Hunter & Ed Hunter about 1917 or 1918 1917 or 1918, 1 neg, 2 photo (Box-folder 042-054)
  - 3 generations of Hunters: Uncle Lamont Hunter, Thomas H. Hunter, & [Ed Hunter] [n.d.], 1 neg, 2 photo (Box-folder 042-055)
  - [Thomas H. Hunter] & unidentified boy in front of a house [n.d.], 1 neg, 2 photo (Box-folder 042-056)
  - Thomas H. Hunter as a Harvard undergrad, Niles, MI 1934 or 33?, 2 photo, 1 neg (Box-folder 042-057)
  - Thomas H. Hunter, approximately 9-11 years old [n.d.], 2 photo, 1 neg (Box-folder 042-058)
  - [Thomas H. Hunter] as an infant [n.d.], 2 photo, 1 neg (Box-folder 042-059)
  - Argyra Hunter with infant Thomas [H. Hunter] 1913, 2 photo, 1 neg (Box-folder 042-060)
  - Tom White, Argy's brother after whom Thomas H. Hunters was named [n.d.], 1 neg, 2 photo (Box-folder 042-061)
  - Edwin L Hunter, 1890s The Young Doctor 1890s, 2 photo, 1 neg (Box-folder 042-062)
  - [s.n. Hunter] [n.d.], 2 photo, 1 neg (Box-folder 042-063)
  - [Argyle? Hunter] [n.d.], 2 photo, 1 neg (Box-folder 042-064)
  - [s.n. Hunter] [n.d.], 2 photos, 1 neg (Box-folder 042-065)
  - Florence Patcher Hunter, L.K. Hunter's wife [n.d.], 2 photo, 1 neg (Box-folder 042-066)
  - Jessie Hunter about 1890 1890s, 2 photo, 1 neg (Box-folder 042-067)
  - Unidentified man [possibly Dr. Henry B. Mulholland] [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-068)
  - Dr. [W.C.] Dabney [1890s], 1 neg, 1 photo (Box-folder 042-069)
  - Dr. Henry B. Mulholland [n.d.], 2 photo (Box-folder 042-070)
  - Dr. Byrd S. Leavell [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-071)
  - [Dr. Kenneth R. Crispell], [Dr. Byrd S. Leavell], & [Dr. Charles Crockett] [1965], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-072)
  - Group photo of 18 individuals, honoring Bryd W. Leavell's contribution to the Medical Library [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-073)
  - [Dr. Kenneth R. Crispell] Summer 1958, 2 photo (Box-folder 042-074)
  - [Dr. Kenneth R. Crispell] speaking at a banquet [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-075)
  - [Dr. Kenneth R. Crispell] [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-076)
  - Dr. Kenneth R. Crispell, unidentified man, & an award [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-077)
  - Dr. Oscar A. Thorup, Jr. April 1955, 1 photo (Box-folder 042-078)
  - [Byrd S. Leavell] [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-079)
  - [Byrd S. Leavell] [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-080)
  - Dr. [William H.] Parson 1966-67, 1 photo (Box-folder 042-081)
  - Dr. [William H.] Parson 1966-67, 1 photo (Box-folder 042-082)
  - Dr. [William H.] Parson 1966-67, 1 photo (Box-folder 042-083)
  - Group Photo, unknown location [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-084)
  - Group Photo with 21 individuals including Dr. Oscar Swineford, Jr. [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-085)
  - Dr. J. Edwin Wood, Jr. [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-086)
  - [Dr. J. Edwin Wood, Jr.] [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-087)
  - [Dr. Oscar Swineford, Jr.] [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-088)
  - [Dr. Oscar Swineford, Jr.] [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-089)
  - Group photo of six men [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-090)
  - Wintery UVa scene [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-091)
  - Aerial shot of UVa Medical Center April 9, 1980, 1 photo (Box-folder 042-092)
  - The Lawn, Uva [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-093)
  - The Lawn [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-094)
  - Vickie O'Neill, R.N., University Medical Associates [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-095)
  - Reception & lobbey in one of the medical departments [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-096)
  - Doctor taking the pulse of an elderly patient [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-097)
  - Medical Instrument [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-098)
  - Medical Instrument with with elderly patient in background [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-099)
  - Female Medical Staff with three individuals [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-100)
  - Unidentified man in laboratory [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-101)
  - Doctor listening to the lungs of a male teenage patient [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-102)
  - Hands, getting finger pricked [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-103)
  - Hospital worker exams medical machine [n.d.], 1 photo (Box-folder 042-104)
  - B. Wood, signed to [Thomas Hunter] [n.d.], 3 photos, 1 negative (Box-folder 043-001)
    Re: From the photograph collection of Thomas Hunter; Hook conducted a series of interviews with him.
  - Unidentified man in a boat [n.d.], 2 slides, 1 photo (Box-folder 043-002)
  - Unidentified man [n.d.], 2 photos, 1 negative (Box-folder 043-003)
  - John H. [s.n.] [n.d.], 2 photos, 1 negative (Box-folder 043-004)
  - Unidentified man [n.d.], 2 slides, 1 photo (Box-folder 043-005)
  - Group Photograph, Cambridge University Rowing Crew, including Thomas Hunter November 30, 1935, 1 photo (Box-folder 043-006)
  - Unidentified man [n.d.], 1 photo, 1 negative (Box-folder 043-007)
  - 2 unidentified men [n.d.], 2 photos, 1 negative (Box-folder 043-008)
  - Unidentified man [n.d.], 2 photos, 1 negative (Box-folder 043-009)
  - Unknown male with microscope [n.d.], 2 photos, 1 negative (Box-folder 043-010)
  - Unknown male [n.d.], 2 photos, 1 negative (Box-folder 043-011)
  - Unknown male [n.d.], 2 photos, 1 negative (Box-folder 043-012)
  - Unknown man [n.d.], 2 photos, 1 negative (Box-folder 043-013)
  - Group Photograph of 14 men - Thomas Hunter in center [n.d.], 2 photos, 1 negative (Box-folder 043-014)
  - Group photo of 27 doctors; Thomas Hunter (1st person in 1st row) [n.d.], 2 photos, 1 negative (Box-folder 043-015)
  - Bob [s.n.], inscribed to [Thomas Hunter] [n.d.], 2 photo, 1 negative (Box-folder 043-016)
  - [Thomas Hunter?] as a young boy [n.d.], 1 photo, 1 negative (Box-folder 043-017)
  - Thomas Hunter [3rd from right], a nurse, and 2 other men in an office [n.d.], 2 photos, 1 negative (Box-folder 043-018)
  - Thomas Hunter visiting with two men [n.d.], 1 photo, 1 negative (Box-folder 043-019)
  - "The Webster Gloved ? Society" - [Thomas Hunter] 2nd from left January, 27, 1950, 1 photo, 1 neg (Box-folder 043-020)
  - Stethoscope [n.d.], 1 artifact (Box-folder 043-021)
    Stethoscope used by Dr. Edward W. Hook.
  - Stethoscope [n.d.], 1 artifact (Box-folder 043-022)
  - The Lumica Stethoscope [n.d.], 1 artifact (Box-folder 044-001)
    The Lumica Sprague Rapport Stethoscope is advertised as 5 stethoscopes in one.
  - 16 mm color film: Dr. Hook, Arlan Shilan October 6, 1972, 1 artifact (Box-folder 044-002)
  - Film: Cholera Today: Beside Evaluation & Treatment [n.d.], 1 artifact (Box-folder 044-003)
    Film produced by the National Audiovisual Center, Washington, D.C. 20409
  - Film: Warner's Syndrome, Dr. Hook [n.d.], 1 artifact (Box-folder 044-004)
    Discussion of Warner's Syndrome by Dr. Hook.
  - Glass tube [n.d.], 1 artifact (Box-folder 044-005)
    Glass tube with glass stopper and a plastic valve.